floship.com 2018-09-29

# Privacy Policy - Floship

​We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy. We value the trust that you place in us by providing to us your personal data and we are committed to taking all reasonable precautions to protect your personal data from misuse and keeping it secure by complying with all applicable data protection laws and regulations in Hong Kong, as amended from time to time. We regularly review this Privacy Policy and may revise it from time to time by updating this page. By continuing to use our services after any amendments being made to this Privacy Policy (if any), you are agreeing to the revised Privacy Policy. Please read on for more details on our policies and practices in relation to personal data.

We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy. We value the trust that you place in us by providing to us your personal data and we are committed to taking all reasonable precautions to protect your personal data from misuse and keeping it secure by complying with all applicable data protection laws and regulations in Hong Kong, as amended from time to time. We regularly review this Privacy Policy and may revise it from time to time by updating this page. By continuing to use our services after any amendments being made to this Privacy Policy (if any), you are agreeing to the revised Privacy Policy. Please read on for more details on our policies and practices in relation to personal data.

 **1\. Your consent**

 **​**  

By using our services and website, you are consenting to our collecting, using and disclosing your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. When we collect your personal data, we will provide you with a “personal information collection statement” on or before the collection. If you do not agree to such collection, use and disclosure, please do not use our services or website or otherwise provide us with your personal data.

We will only collect, use or disclose your personal data where it is fair and lawful to do so. In most cases, we will ask for your consent explicitly; however, in some cases, we may infer consent from your actions and behaviour. You are not obliged to provide such consent, but without such consent, our services to you may be limited. 

 **2\. Collection of your Personal Data**

 **​**  

We may collect your personal data online through our website ([www.floship.com](https://www.floship.com/)) or via other means (including our physical stores, direct marketing or application for use of our services) and use of such personal data will help us add more products and services of interest to you and also to ensure that your shopping experience with us is an enjoyable and a personalized one.

Provision of personal data online

When you register or place an order with us or receive various features or services that we offer online through our website or participate in other online or social media activities, we may collect personal data such as your name, contact details and payment/credit card information, or any other personal data you voluntarily provide to us, as the case maybe.

We will only collect personal data which we believe to be necessary to fulfill the Purposes (defined hereinbelow). The provision of such personal data is voluntary. However, we may not be able to fulfill the Purposes (defined hereinbelow) and provide services to you if such personal data have not been provided. We may contact you to verify the accuracy of the personal data provided by you and will not retain your personal data longer than necessary to fulfill the Purposes (defined hereinbelow).

 **3\. Purpose of collection**

 **​**  

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to better serve our users.

We use the personal data collected from you for the following purposes (“Purposes”):

  1. assessing, verifying and administering your data (including processing your membership registration/application and allowing you to participate in our marketing, promotional and corporate activities);
  2. fulfilling your orders for products and services you may make with us (including maintaining your shopping cart on our website, order processing and payment clearing);
  3. handling and responding to your inquiries, suggestions or complaints;
  4. direct marketing (please refer to paragraph 6 below for more details);
  5. conducting analysis to help us better understand you and to improve our services and products; and
  6. any other purposes directly related to the above.

 **4\. Transfer of personal data**

We may disclose or transfer your personal data to our related companies (including our holding companies and/or affiliated companies) or any third party service providers, whether within or outside Hong Kong, as necessary on a need-to-know basis to fulfill any of the Purposes. We may also disclose or transfer your personal data to any other party when we believe such disclosure or transfer is mandatory for legal reasons or where it is necessary to protect our interests (as permitted by law).

We will not disclose or transfer your personal data as stated above unless we have obtained your prior express consent. You may indicate your preference where appropriate or request us to change your preference (without any fees), at any time by contacting our Customer Service Representative in accordance with paragraph 12 hereinbelow. We will comply with all applicable data protection laws and regulations in Hong Kong, as amended from time to time, to safeguard the personal data we disclose or transfer.

 **5\. Retention of personal data**

We will retain your personal data for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the Purposes for which the personal data is to be used and erase any of your personal data that we have stored as soon as reasonably practicable, subject to, or where otherwise required by law or permitted by law.

 **6\. Direct marketing**

We intend to use your personal data for marketing activities (“Marketing Activities”) from time to time, including 

(i) marketing our products and services, activities, contests, promotional offers (benefits and privileges), special events and any other information which we think may be of relevance, or sending out free product samples; and 

(ii) marketing products and services, activities, contests, promotional offers (benefits and privileges) and special events of our vendors, business partners or third party service providers; and 

(iii) conducting researches and evaluation.

Such Marketing Activities may be provided to you in various methods in accordance with the personal data you provide to us, including advertisement, postal mail, telephone call, email, text or messages on your wireless or mobile device.

We will not use your personal data for Marketing Activities unless we obtain your prior express consent. You may partially or entirely opt-out of receiving information in relation to Marketing Activities by indicating your preference where appropriate or request us to change your preference (without any fees), at any time by contacting our Customer Service Representative in accordance with paragraph 12 hereinbelow.

 **7\. Protection of Information**

 **​**  

To protect your personal data while you are using our website, we use sophisticated encryption technology and secured servers to keep your personal data safe. All your ordering information is protected during transmission by using the Secure Sockets Layer, which encrypts the information that you input so that it cannot be read in transit. Other security measures include restricting access to personal data to employees who have a need to use the data and who have been trained to handle such data properly and observe confidentiality. No unauthorized access will be allowed.

 **8\. Cookies**

 **​**  

We use cookies to automatically collect information about you when you visit our website (such as the type of the internet browser and operating system you are using and the domain name of your internet service provider). Cookies are small pieces of information that your web browser stores on your computer when you visit a website. Our cookies identify your computer to us and allow us to personalize your shopping experience and recognize you when you return. Information collected from these cookies may be used for the Purposes set out in paragraph 3 hereinabove.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You may choose to disable cookies on your computer by changing your browser’s settings. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to use all features and services offered on our website.

 **9\. Websites of third parties**

 **​**  

This Privacy Policy only applies to us and our website, but not to any other third parties (including any websites maintained by them). When you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to either third parties’ websites or websites of companies associated with us, you will be subject to the privacy policies of those parties. Whilst we support the protections of privacy on the internet, we do not accept responsibility for any actions taken by third parties outside our web domain.

 **10\. Rights of access and update of personal data**

 **​**  

You may check whether we hold any of your personal data and, if so, you may also request access, verify, update or correct, or request a copy of your personal data held by us by contacting our Customer Service Representative in accordance with paragraph 12 hereinbelow. We will verify your identity before handling your request and a reasonable fee may be charged for complying with such request. We endeavour to respond to you within a reasonable time.

 **11\. Changes to our Privacy Policy**

 **​**  

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the updated version of the Privacy Policy on our website ([www.floship.com](https://www.floship.com/)). We encourage you to visit frequently to stay informed of our most updated version.

 **12\. Further Information**

 **​**  

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact our Customer Service Representatives via our Contact Us page.
